unichange.me 2018-09-21

# Privacy Policy | Unichange.me

## Overview

Here at Unichange.me we understand the importance of keeping your personal data safe. This Privacy Policy outlines the way Unichange.me service collects, handles, stores, shares and protects your personal information. “Personal information” or “personal data” means any information that can be used to identify a person including, but not limited to e-mail, name, surname, phone number, physical or postal address and other personally identifiable information. 

We encourage you to familiriarise yourself with our Privacy Policy to understand how your data is processed, as well as your rights regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By submitting your information, you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy. 

Your personal information will be processed, stored and protected according to the EU General Data Protection Regulation – GDPR, Regulation 216/679/EU, effective 25.05.2018. 

We are obliged to keep the personal data minimum of 5 years, unless there is a particular reason to hold the records for longer in order to fulfill our contractual, regulatory and statutory obligations. 

If you have any queries concerning your personal data or any requests in respect of these practices, please feel free to contact us via our e-mail address [support@unichange.me](mailto:support@unichange.me). 

Unichange.me service may update this Privacy Policy from time to time therefore it is recommended to review our Privacy Policy when visiting our website repeatedly. We will post the changes on this page and may notify our customers via News section on our website or inform you via e-mail so that you may be aware of the changes. Your continued use of this site following any changes to this Privacy Policy will mean you accept those changes. 

## 1\. What information we collect

This Privacy Policy applies to all countries we work with. Personal information is collected when you provide personal data to the website Unichange.me, for example when you register, verify your Unichange account, use Unichange.me services with or without authorization, submit a ticket or contact us via Live chat. 

We may collect the following information about you: 

  * personal and contact information that may include, but not limited to your email address, full name, date of birth, nationality, address, telephone number, bank account details or payment account details when you register an account with us;
  * your registered name, registered office address, certificate of incorporation, certificate of incumbency, certificate of good standing, memorandum of association, articles of association, list of current shareholders, list of current directors, identification and proof of address of beneficial owners, directors and any power of attorney if you verify an account for a corporate entity;
  * information that is indicated in your documents provided for account verification (copies of your national identity card, passport, driving license or other government issued photo-ID);
  * information about your transactions on our service when you place an order with our without authorization;
  * technical information including your IP-address, login information, type and version of browser, your location, operating platform and system when you interact with our website; information about your visit, including the full URL clickstream (including date and time); pages you view; page response times, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information;
  * records of your correspondence with Unichange.me that was sent by e-mail, ticket system or via Live chat;

## 2\. How we collect and process your personal information

2.1 We collect the above-mentioned information by the means of: 
  * your direct interactions with our service (when you register and verify Unichange.me account, contact us via e-mail or Live chat, place an order on our service, subscribe to our Newsletter, give us feedback, reply to our survey or take part in competition held by Unichange.me);
  * cookies and other tracking technologies (when you visit our website or login to your account);
third party partners (such as our analytics and advertising providers such as Google; business partners, payment systems or merchant partners). 

2.2 Unichange.me will use your personal information only in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

We process your personal data to: 

  * register your account with us;
  * identify your personality for secure transactions;
  * provide you with a more personalized service;
  * improve our website, advertising, services, customer support;
  * perform market research to analyze the effectiveness of provided advertisement;
  * send you special offers and promotions via e-mail or SMS;
  * send important information regarding changes to our services, terms and conditions, privacy policy, news and notifications via e-mail;
  * hold your information for security administration, legal and maintenance purposes;
  * monitor and evaluate to prevent fraud, money laundering, financing terrorism and any other financial crimes;
  * share aggregated information with third parties (such as our merchant partners, banks, payment systems) for advertising and promotional purposes and to provide our services to you. We will not pass on your individual contact details unless you have given us specific permission to do so.
  
We also reserve the right to collect usage and access data that allows us to prevent multiple account openings or other fraudulent actions, it is performed for protection our systems against illegal attacks or abuse. 

## 3\. How your information is stored and secured

Unichange.me is commited to protecting the personal information you provide to us. We take every effort to protect your personal data from misuse, interference, loss, unauthorised access, modification or disclosure. 

We store the provided information on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using Secure Sockets Layered (SSL) technology. As you are on the Internet that cannot be completely secure we recommend you to take every precaution in protecting your personal information. You are responsible for keeping this password confidential. Please make sure you use strong password that is combination of numbers and letters, change it often, activate 2-Step Authentication in your account, use a secure browser and do not reveal your login details to anyone. 

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to a destination outside the European Economic Area (EEA). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing outside the EEA. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure adequate security for your personal data. Your data may be transferred to third parties we work with outside EEA providing sufficient and appropriate safeguards to your personal data. We will ensure that all companies to which your Personal Data is disclosed will only process it to the extent we ourselves are entitled, in accordance with our instructions and on our behalf. 

## 4\. Third-Party websites

Our website may contain links to third-party websites and other Internet resources. When clicking the link you are visiting another website. Please note that these websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy. We recommend to review Privacy Policy of each website you visit as these services are outside our control. 

## 5\. Cookies and other tracking technologies

Unichange.me and our third-party partners, such as our advertising and analytics partners, use cookies and other tracking technologies to distinguish you from other website users. 

A cookie is a small file that is stored on your browser or the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. This information allows us to improve our site and provide you with a good experience when you browse our website. Also, cookies can be used to store your password for more comfortable entering to your account. 

## 6\. Your rights

Where we process your personal data, you have a number of rights over how the data is processed and can exercise these rights at any point. These rights include the rights set out below: 
  * The right to have access to your personal data.
  
You can exercise this right by contacting us via Contact Us form. Your request will be reviewed within 40 days. You may be charged a reasonable fee (as permitted by the GDPR) for this information. 
  * The right to rectification of your personal data.
  
You have the right to correct or update your personal information at any time. This enables you to correct any incomplete or inaccurate data we hold about you, though we may need to verify the accuracy of the new data you provide to us. 
  * The right to restrict processing.
  
Under certain circumstances, you have the right to restrict the processing of your personal data. By exercising this right you can limit the way your data is processed. The restricted data will not be used in any way except to store it.  
In case you restrict the data that is mandatory to be provided, we may not be able to provide you with our services. 
  * The right to object processing.
  
Under certain circumstances, you have the right to object to certain types of data processing, including processing for direct marketing (i.e. the communication to you of any advertising or marketing material). This right is not an absolute and can be overridden if we have legitimate grounds to use the data. 
  * The right to data portability.
  
The personal data you provide to us is portable. This means it can be moved, copied or transmitted electronically under certain circumstances. You can request the transfer of your personal data to you or to a third party. 
  * The right to withdraw your consent.
  
You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where we are relying on your consent to process your personal information. However, this will not affect the lawfulness of any processing carried out before you withdraw your consent. In case you withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide certain services to you. You will be notified if this is the case at the time you contact us for consent withdrawal. 
  * The right to refuse.
  
You can refuse to provide us with the personal data which we request from you. If, however, this involves information which must be compulsorily provided, we will be unable to provide you with the associated services. 
  * The right to request erasure of your personal data.
  
You have the right to request erasure of your personal information provided to our service. Your request will be reviewed within one month of receipt. The right is not absolute and does not apply if processing of data is necessary in certain circumstances, for example to comply with a legal obligation or for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims. 

## 7\. Disclosure of your personal information

Unichange.me uses your personal information to operate your Unichange.me personal account and provide you services offered on the website unichange.me. We also share certain information with banks, merchants, payment systems, debit card vendors and identity verification services as part of our regular daily business operations. 

The purpose of sharing personal data is to identify and verify our customers, to process your orders, to limit fraudulent actions and other criminal activities, also it is necessary to manage our financial risk. Your personal data disclosed to any partner-company will be processed only in accordance with Unichange.me instructions and on Unichange.me behalf. We will guarantee that the data will be used only to the extent to which we ourselves are entitled. 

Unichange.me will use the remarketing or similar audiences feature in AdWords. This feature is used for advertisement only. Third-party vendors, including Google, will show advertisement of Unichange.me on their AdSense page. To be able to show ads based on preferences of people, who visited Unichange.me before, third-party vendors, including Google, will use cookies. Visitors can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Ads Preferences Manager. 

If necessary or authorised by law, we may disclose your personal information to regulatory organisations, law enforcement agencies, courts or other public authorities. We will make an effort to inform you about legal demands for your personal information except the cases when it is prohibited by law or court order or the inquiry shall be handled within the shortest period of time. 

Should you have any questions or queries regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us via Contact Us page or [support@unichange.me](mailto:support@unichange.me) e-mail.
